I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
（真帆(まほ)）コユキがBECK(ベック)の復活を—
You're seriously thinking
about the revival of BECK,
マジに考えてるからさ…
私も力になれるかな～って
so I wondered if I could help.
And what did Chiba-kun say?
（コユキ）で… 千葉(ちば)君は何て？
You will be dead!
（千葉）
ユー ウィル ビー デッド！
The conversation ended
in the worst way possible.
（真帆）話し合いは
壮絶なバッドエンドを迎えたわ
（コユキ）
フッ… 千葉君らしいね
It's so like Chiba-kun.
-This is nothing to laugh at!
-Mmm.
（真帆）
笑うことじゃないじゃん！
-Still...That ramen is bad!
-That ramen is bad!
（真帆）それにしても…
（コユキ・真帆）
まずいよね あそこのラーメン…
"Condor Ramen"
（コユキ）こんにちは
（千葉）おう
Hello!
-Hey...
-Chiba-kun, I...
（コユキ）千葉君… 実は…
Were you the one who sent Maho?
（千葉）あれか？ 真帆のヤツ
差し向けたのは てめえか？
Were you the one who sent Maho?
Huh...Err, no...
（コユキ）え… あっ いや…
ホント 言いたいこと
さんざん言いやがって！
Hah! Spouting her mouth off!
真帆は何て？
What did Maho say?
That there's no future
in bad-tasting ramen...
（千葉）“まずいラーメンに
未来はないから—”
so I should join up
with BECK when they regroup.
“再結成するBECKに
参加しろ！”ってさ…
あいつ 一方的に叫んでたぜ
That's all she kept saying.
Chiba-kun!
千葉君
Huh?
Let's revive BECK...one more time.
もう一度 BECK やろう！
Huh?
（コユキ）と言っても
今は まだ俺 １人きりだけど
Well...I'm the only one right now...
（千葉）ワリィな
Sorry, but right now...
I can only think about ramen.
今はラーメンのことしか
頭にねえんだ
（千葉）おい！ コユキ！
（コユキ）ん？
Hey, Koyuki!
（千葉）うちのラーメン
そんなにまずいか？
Is my ramen...that bad?
Yeah...
（千葉）お前…
本気でBECKを？
Are you serious about BECK?
その… 何ていうか…
I have to be serious...
or there won't be another BECK!
（コユキ）本気でなきゃ—
BECKは できないよ！
（千葉）戻ってもいいのか？
（コユキ）あっ
I can come back?
（千葉）
夢を見てなくても いいのか？
I don't have to have a dream?
What're you saying, Chiba-kun?!
（コユキ）何 言ってんだよ
千葉君！
（千葉）お… おせえよ お前！
You're so late!
I've been regretting it since
the day after Grateful Sound...
俺 グレイトフルサウンドの
翌日から後悔しまくりでよ
Why'd that...
何で あんなこと…
（コユキ）千葉君！
Chiba-kun!
（千葉）けどな
竜介(りゅうすけ)とは仲直りしねえぞ！
But I can't make it up with Ryusuke!
Chiba-kun...
（コユキ）千葉君…
（コユキ）平(たいら)君 すごい…
Taira-kun is awesome!
（千葉）すげえな このバンド
That band was something else!
（真帆）もう！ 早くしないと
平君 行っちゃうよ！
Hurry it up before Taira leaves!
（千葉）ああ…
でも そう焦ってもさあ
Yeah...But if we're too hasty...
Taira-kun!
（コユキ）平君！
Hey, nice to see you.
（平）よう 久しぶり
Taira...Yoshiaki's calling for you.
（山中）平～
ヨシアキが下で呼んでるぞ
Be right there.
ああ すぐ行く
-Actually, I wanted to ask you
to return to BECK once...
-I got it.
（コユキ）実は…
もう一度 BECKに戻っ…
分かった
（コユキ）え!?
-Huh?
-You're regrouping BECK?
BECK やるんだろ？
Yes.
I was planning to agree only
if you came to see me.
コユキが誘いに来た時だけ
ＯＫするつもりだった
（コユキ）平君…
-Taira-kun...
-Hey, hey...
（千葉）平君～！
-Taira-kun!
-Idiot!
バカ！
（千葉）アハハ…
（平）今はヒーロウズの
一員だから—
I'm a member of Heroes now,
so I can't commit immediately.
すぐにってのは無理だけど—
ツアーとプロモーションが
終わったら何とかするよ
After the promotional tour,
I'll work it out with them.
Taira-kun...
（真帆）平君…
（平）ただし
俺が戻るのは あくまでも—
However...I'm agreeing to return...
...on the condition that all
five original members come back.
オリジナルメンバー５人
集まった場合だけだぜ
Huh?!
（平）それ以外では
一切 関わりたくない
Otherwise, I want nothing
to do with this.
（千葉）平君…
Taira-kun...
Sorry, but I'm busy. See ya.
（平）悪いな
俺は忙しいんだ じゃっ！
Well then, the big problem
here is Ryusuke.
こうなると 問題は竜介だね
Yeah...
あいつ もう
日本にいねえんじゃねえかな？
Maybe...he's no longer in Japan.
Even if he's away,
I think our spirit is one.
離れてても みんなの思いは
１つだと思うんだ
（ペイジ）アホー アホー
"Saito Paper Company"
Koyuki-kun, can you throw this out?
（斎藤(さいとう)）コユキ君
これ 捨ててきてね
（コユキ）はい！
"Saito Paper Company"
Sure.
うっ… ふんっ… ああ！
ハァ…
Koyuki-kun, can you go shopping?
（斎藤）コユキ君
それじゃあ 買い物行ってきて
I have a date with Momo-chan.
僕は桃(もも)ちゃんとデートだから
（コユキ）はあ…
All right.
（ペイジ）
アホー！ コユキ アホー
"Chinese Restaurant Sing Lung"
（コユキ）フゥ…
I'm back.
（コユキ）ただいまー
Oh, welcome home...
（コユキの母）あら おかえり
Was there a phone call for me?
（コユキ）何か電話あった？
（コユキの母）いや なかったよ
No, there wasn't.
（コユキ）そう…
I see.
（千葉）ウワー！ ハハハー！
ヤッハー！ フゥー！ ヤーッ！
（千葉）いやぁ
すげえライブだったよ
Man, that was a fantastic
live performance!
If you told me you were coming,
I'd have put you down as guests.
（平）来るって言ってくれたら
ゲストに入れておいたのに
（女性）平さん
Taira-san, will you
take a picture with me?
あの… 一緒に写真
撮ってもらっていいですか？
Sure.
（平）ああ いいよ
This is from Koyuki.
これ コユキからだぜ
ヘヘヘヘへ…
おい 千葉！
Hey, Chiba!
Don't keep your fan waiting,
you sexy rocker!
（千葉）ファンの女の子を
待たすんじゃねえよ！
この色男！
Idiot!
バカ！
コユキのヤツ…
That Koyuki...
There's a strange rumor
spreading among the fans.
（山中）最近 ファンの間で—
妙なウワサが
ささやかれているんだけど…
Yeah...Something about you
leaving Heroes after the tour.
（ヨシアキ）そうなんだよ
平がツアー終了とともに
ヒーロウズを抜けるらしいってさ
To rejoin BECK.
BECKを再結成するってさ
I mean, geez...
（山中）だよな
インディーズながら
20万枚を売り上げる—
Why would anyone quit Heroes,
which is gonna sell 200,000 CDs?
ヒーロウズを辞めるなんてなあ
Hey, Taira!
（ヨシアキ）おい 平？
Wanna listen?
（平）聞いてみる？
（山中・ヨシアキ）え？
-Huh?
（平）荒削りだけど
才能がキラキラしてる
It's a rough cut.
But the genius shines through.
I'm amazed he wrote so many songs.
しかも よくこんなに
書きためたな あいつ…
Huh?
For everything up to now,
thank you so much!
今までホントにありがとう
Think of me as a fool.
バカだと思ってください
But I'm going to return to BECK.
俺はＢＥＣＫに
戻ります
（山中）ウソだろ
マジで？
-Are you kidding?!
-No shit?!
（ジョン・リー・デイビス）
〈ヘイ！ リュースケ・ミナミ！〉
Hey, Ryusuke Minami!
Ho man, what a surprise!
〈驚いたぜ！〉
How long you been here
in New York?
〈いったい いつから
ニューヨークに？〉
Mr. Davis...
（南 竜介）
〈ミスターデイビス！〉
Okay, Ryusuke Minami...
（デイビス）〈オーケー！
リュースケ・ミナミ！〉
〈私で力になれるなら協力しよう〉
If I can help, I'll give you a hand.
（竜介）〈感謝します
ミスターデイビス！〉
I really appreciate it, Mr. Davis.
Doitashimashite. [You're welcome]
（デイビス）ドウイタシマシテ！
Yukio! Phone call!
（コユキの母）幸雄！ 電話よ！
（コユキ）はーい！
Okay!
Hello?
Huh?! Yeah.
（コユキ）ハァ ハァ…
んっ ハァ ハァ…
ハァ ハァ ハァ…
（サク）お待たせ！ コユキ
Sorry to keep you waiting, Koyuki.
ん… サク！
-Saku!
-It took me a while
to save enough money.
（サク）なかなか
お金が たまらなくてさ
（コユキ）遅いよ！
You're late!
あっ ゴメン
-Sorry.
-I was so worried!
（コユキ）
すごく心配してたんだぞ！
コユキ…
Koyuki...
（コユキ）最近 連絡も
あんまり来ないし…
You haven't been
in touch lately, either.
（サク）もっと早く
来たかったんだけどね
I wanted to come earlier...
（コユキ）サク～
Saku...
Koyuki...
（サク）コユキ…
...just have to Stage Dive or Die
Mind blower, a shower of sweat
Run towards a new world, my life
Those who seek it will be rewarded
Pass the hot shot
Keep on coming, come on!
Blow your mind
Squeeze your sweat yeah
（千葉）おめえんちのおやじ
頑固だもんな
Your old man is stubborn.
結局 おやじを説得できなくて
飛び出してきちゃったバイ
I couldn't convince him,
had'ta run away.
Had'ta?
（コユキ）バイって…
（平）アパートが決まるまで—
You can stay at my house for as long
as it takes to find an apartment.
好きなだけ
俺んちに いていいぞ
I'm sa'happy.
うれしいバイ
Sa'happy?
（コユキ）バイって…
Uh! Typhoon! Typhoon 24!
24-7! Non-stop...
（コユキの母）幸雄！
佐藤(さとう)って人から電話よ！
Yukio, there's a phone call
from someone named Sato.
All right!
（コユキ）はーい！
Hello?
（和緒(かずお)）
BECK復活 おめでとう
Congratulations on the revival of BECK!
O-Oh, thank you.
（コユキ）あ ありがとう
I'll get right to the point.
（和緒）手短に用件を伝えるわね
Yes?
（和緒）あんたたちBECKに—
There's an offer for BECK
for an American tour.
アメリカツアーのオファーが
来てるのよ
America?
（コユキ）アメリカ？
（レオン）ハロー
Hello?
Hey, what's up?
（竜介）〈やぁ ごきげんかい？〉
〈ジョンから聞いてかけた〉
I heard about you from John.
〈あんたと取引がしたい〉
I want to make a deal with you.
I have a most valuable tape here
which I got from Eddy Lee.
〈すげえ価値のあるテープを
持ってる〉
〈エディからもらった〉
I'll give you this,
〈これを渡す代わりに—〉
instead I want you to leave
Mongolian Chop Squad alone forever.
〈二度とモンゴリアン・チョップ・
スクワッドには—〉
〈手を出さないでほしい〉
Right. Some deal...
（レオン）
〈ムシのいい話だな〉
（竜介）〈今夜 あんたのホテルに
テープを持っていく〉
I'll bring the tape to
your hotel tonight anyway.
You sure are a crazy dumb ass.
（レオン）
〈相変わらずクレイジーなヤツだ〉
If you never change
I think there is no way my life fizzle out
You open up the door with negative aura
(I'm fed up fed up fed up)
You say future is murky indeed...
I'm sick of hearing gripe.
（千葉）全米ツアーって…
An American tour?!
すっげえじゃん！
That's unbelievable!
Does that mean we
can throw television sets
じゃあ ツェッペリンや
ストーンズみたいに—
out the window like
Lead Zeppelin and the Stones...
ホテルの部屋から
テレビ投げたり—
and fly around in groovy jets and stuff?
専用ジェットで
グルーピーたちと—
あんなことや こんなこと
できんのか!?
Idiot! It's a hard tour...driving across
ten cities to perform in rock venues.
（平）バーカ 車で全米何十か所もの
ライブハウスを縦断する—
過酷なツアーだよ
-Ohh...
-Still, it's unbelievable.
（サク）それにしても
やっぱり すごいよね
（コユキ）
グレイトフルサウンドで—
A band member of
a group called F.V.E.
Saw us at Grateful Sound
and made the offer.
俺たちを見た
Ｆ.Ｖ.Ｅ.ってバンドの人が—
誘ってくれたんだよ
（千葉）こりゃ やるしかねえな！
-We've gotta do it!
-Think carefully!
（平）よく考えてみろ
Huh?!
Without Ryusuke...it's too risky
for BECK to do an American tour.
（平）竜介のいない 今のBECKでの
アメリカツアーは危険すぎる
（千葉）けどよ…
But...
（コユキ）
こんなチャンス断るなんて—
It's not like us to turn down
a chance like this!
俺たちらしくないよ！
（平）危険な賭けだな
But it's dangerous.
America, huh...
（千葉）アメリカか…
（コユキ）パスポート作らなきゃ
-We'd better get passports.
-Does that cost money?
（千葉）それって 金かかるの？
Summer vacation ended with BECK
rehearsals day in and day out.
（コユキ）BECKの練習に
明け暮れた夏休みは—
瞬く間に過ぎていった
Man, look how dark you got!
（男子生徒１）
お前 真っ黒じゃん！
And you're so white!
（男子生徒２）お前は白いな
-Shaddup!
-Koyuki-kun, Saku-chan told me...
（益岡(ますおか)）コユキ君
サクちゃんから聞いたけど
ホントに学校辞めるの？
But are you really
dropping out of school?
Yeah.
（益岡）コユキ君…
Koyuki-kun...
I was hoping to
just fade out slowly...
（コユキ）自然なフェードアウトを
狙ってたんだけど—
But with the American tour coming up,
I figured it's good timing.
アメリカツアーもあるし
いいタイミングかなって
Aww...It'll be lonely without you guys.
（益岡）あ～あ さみしくなるな…
Sorry.
（コユキ）ゴメン
（益岡）アメリカか…
遠すぎて行けないよ
America, huh?
It's too far, I can't go.
Farewell!
さらば！
This is an announcement
from the Student Council.
（アナウンス）生徒会からの
お知らせがあります
26日の15時から…
On the 26th from 3pm...
...my sister.
（コユキ）アメリカツアー前の
怒濤(どとう)のライブ週間が始まった
...my sister.
We began exhausting live performances
to prepare for the American Tour.
In this world, which everyone is lonely.
We began exhausting live performances
to prepare for the American Tour.
In this world, which everyone is lonely.
Yeah.
If you are at a loss as to what to do.
Raise you stiff middle finger.
It will know which way the wind blows.
Our last performance was at the Marquee.
（コユキ）
ラストを締めくくったのは—
マーキーだ
（千葉）俺たちの
次回のライブの告知は…
Our next live performance in town...
なーい！
None!
Because BECK is starting a grueling 50-day,
46-city tour of the United States!
（千葉）BECKは来週から—
50日間 46か所巡り
地獄の全米ツアーに旅立ちます！
-BECK is the best!
-Chiba!
（女性客）BECK サイコー！
Uh! Typhoon! Typhoon 24!
24-7! Non-stop...
（コユキ）このライブ—
For this last live performance,
Chiba dove into the audience for the close.
最後に千葉君が客席にダイブして
幕を閉じた
（千葉）メチャ イテかったです
はい…
Man, that was painful! Yes.
Huh? How was BECK?
（コユキ）え BECKは どう？
Your guitar was great.
（兵藤(ひょうどう)マサル）田中のギター
すげえ良かったぜ
Really?
（コユキ）ホント？
Yeah.
See ya.
（サク）ん？
（兵藤）じゃあな
Koyuki, wasn't that...
（サク）コユキ 今のって…
兵藤だよ
ゲストで来てたみたい
Hyodo. He was here as a guest.
バンドやってんのかな？
Is he in a band?
最近 ポシャって—
They disbanded recently
and he's looking for new members.
新しいメンバー
探してるとこだってさ
Oh...
ふ～ん
（コユキ）
アメリカツアー頑張れって
He said good luck
on our American Tour.
Oh yeah?
（サク）そっか
（マネージャー）ふざけんな
Don't kid yourself!
（コユキ）
やっぱり ２か月の休みって…
I guess taking off for two months is...
Damn right!
（マネージャー）当たり前だ
Then I'll have to quit.
（コユキ）
それじゃあ 辞めさせて…
（マネージャー）お前の代わりなんて
すぐ見つかるんだよ
It's easy to replace
someone like you!
Thank you for everything.
（コユキ）今まで
ありがとうございました
（従業員）アメリカか…
America, huh?
あっちのヤツらに
負けんじゃねえぞ
Don't lose to the guys over there!
（コユキ）はい！
Yes!
（真帆）slip out of
Slip out of...
（コユキ）スリップ アウト オブ
Slip out ob.
（真帆）out of！
Out of!
（コユキ）アウト オブ
Out ob.
You're hopeless!
（真帆）もう 全然ダメ！
あした 出発なんだよ？
You leave tomorrow!
If you can't pronounce
something like this,
こんな簡単な発音できないなら—
you'd better not go to America!
アメリカに行かないほうがいいよ！
（コユキ）真帆だって
漢字 苦手じゃん
Well Maho, you have
a hard time writing kanji.
We're not talking about me!
（真帆）その話は関係ないでしょ！
もうちょっと優しくとか
できないのかよ！
Can't you be a little more gentle?
（真帆）悪かったね 優しくなくて
Well, excuse me
for not being gentle.
（コユキ）うるさいんだよ
You're so petty!
You can drop dead
in America, Koyuki!
コユキなんて
アメリカで死んじまえ！
Stupid Maho!
（コユキ）真帆のバカ…
（コユキ）ええ ７時に２名で
予約してた 田中です
This is Tanaka...I had reservations
for 2 at 7 o'clock.
すいませんけど
キャンセルしてください
I'm sorry, but I have to cancel.
すみません
Sorry.
-Koyuki-kun, Maho forgot this.
-Huh?
（タマヨ）
コユキ君 真帆の忘れ物
（コユキ）え？ これって…
This is...
"Lesson Cassette: 'Slip Out', For Koyuki"
Maho...
真帆…
（コユキ）♪「MOON ON THE WATER」
What a fool
I don't know 'bout tomorrow
What it's like to be
（コユキの母）幸雄！
パスポートは ちゃんと持った？
Yukio, do you have your passport?
Yup.
（コユキの母）じゃ お父さんに
挨拶していきな
Then say goodbye to your father.
（コユキ）はい
All right.
（コユキの母）
おばあちゃんに電話… した？
Did you call Grandma?
Yup.
No matter how many times
I look at it, it's a rough schedule.
（平）しかし 何度見ても
厳しいスケジュールだな
（サク）
ホントに50日で回るのかな？
Are we really gonna
make it in 50 days?
What will be will be!
That's all there is to know!
（千葉）なるようになる！
つ～ことだよ なっ！
（コユキ）
えーっと ここかな？
Umm...Is this it?
（真帆）フッ おい
いきなりピンボケかよ
Hey, it's so blurred!
All right, there's the American continent!
（コユキ）おお 見えてきました
アメリカ大陸
（真帆）あれ ジェットの羽か？
-Is that the wing of the jet?
-Uh-huh.
（コユキ）今をときめく—
David Eric of the popular
F.V.E. Band came to pick us up.
Ｆ.Ｖ.Ｅ.のボーカル
デビッド・エリックが—
車で迎えに来てくれました
He's out of focus.
（真帆）
ピントが後ろなんですけど
-This is an alien base.
-No, it's the L.A. Airport.
（コユキ）宇宙人の基地です
（真帆）ロスの空港ね
（コユキ）泊まったホテルです
-Our hotel.
-Hey, pretty nice!
（真帆）へえ～ 結構いいじゃん
（コユキ）良かったのは
ここだけでした
This was the only nice hotel.
えー 勉強中の千葉君
-Umm...Chiba-kun studying.
-Some study.
（真帆）何の勉強だか…
-We performed live here.
-It says Mongolian Chop Squad!
（コユキ）ここでライブをやりました
（真帆）ああ～！
“モンゴリアン・チョップ・
スクワッド”って書いてあんね！
But we just couldn't get it together.
（コユキ）
でも 全然調子が出なくて…
（真帆）あー 客 下向いてるし
-The audience is looking down.
-Chiba is depressed.
（コユキ）落ち込んでる千葉君
（真帆）ハハッ 回してえ！
Put it on spin!
-These are members of other bands.
-Where are you, Koyuki?
（コユキ）対バンの人たちだね
（真帆）コユキ… どこ？
（コユキ）フフ…
-We traveled in this car.
-Saku's practically kissing the windshield!
（コユキ）
この車で移動しました
（真帆）ハハハ チューしてる
サクがチューしてる！
-Hey, lots of people!
-We're not performing.
あ いっぱい人 入ってんじゃん
（コユキ）
これは俺たちじゃないです
（真帆）すごい色の髪だね
-Look at the color of her hair!
-The Lizards. That's a guy.
（コユキ）The(ザ) Lizards(リザーズ) 男です
Huh!?
（コユキ）ＣＤを売りました
結構 売れたんだよね
We sold our CDs.
We sold quite a bit actually.
（真帆）へえ～
Hmm...
-This is the car we traveled in.
-Looks so American.
（コユキ）この車で旅をしました
（真帆）アメリカって感じだね
-We're frogs.
-Silly!
（コユキ）カエルです
（真帆）ハハハ… 変なの
（コユキ）この車で…
（真帆）はいはい
-This is the car...
-I get it already!
（真帆）あ ピエロがいるよ
Hey, are they clowns?
-This live was great.
-But I can't see you.
（コユキ）ここは すごかったよ
（真帆）う～ん
でも 見えないんですけど
（コユキ）すごかった
ロングビーチ 万歳！
It was great! Hurrah for Long Beach!
-We had a session together.
-What're you doing, Koyuki?
みんなでセッションしました
（真帆）何してんの？ コユキ
-Oh, you had a flat tire.
-Yes.
（真帆）あ パンクですね～
（コユキ）はい
That's Chiba-kun.
（コユキ）千葉君です
-Look at the clouds!
-It's more awesome when
you actually see them.
（真帆）すごい雲だね
（コユキ）
本物は もっとすごかったよ
Hmm...
（真帆）へえ～
-Oh, another session?
-Taira-kun was popular even in America.
おっ セッション
（コユキ）平君は
アメリカでもモテモテでした
千葉君です
-And here's Chiba-kun.
-Koyuki, you look so cute.
（真帆）フフ…
コユキ かーわいい
We were near total exhaustion.
（コユキ）みんな
疲れのピークだったところだね
-Looks like fun.
-A short moment of relaxation.
（真帆）楽しそう
（コユキ）つかの間の休息
-Here we are in New York!
-This picture's so dark!
ニューヨークで浮かれてます
（真帆）暗くて分かんねえ
-Taking a stroll in New York.
-Did you eat hot dogs?
（コユキ）ニューヨーク散歩です
（真帆）ホットドッグ食べた？
（コユキ）うん
Yup!
This is CBGB.
The audience is to the right.
ＣＢＧＢです
右が客席です
-And this is...
-That's the man...New York Punk.
（真帆）この人は？
（コユキ）その人です
ニューヨークパンクです
（真帆）ん～ 誰？
Who is he?
He's Kevin Eric. The guitarist
and leader of F.V.E.
（コユキ）彼はケビン・エリック
Ｆ.Ｖ.Ｅ.のギタリストであり
リーダー
-He's David's older brother.
-Hmm...
デビッドの兄さんなんだ
（真帆）へえ～
あ またボケてる
-It's blurred again!
-Well, Kevin's a scary guy.
（コユキ）だって
ケビンって怖いんだもん
（真帆）この人も？
-And this guy...
-Yup, that's...
（コユキ）はい その人です
ええと テキサスかな？
Umm...Texas, I think.
-We even traveled
through a place like this.
-Hmm...
（コユキ）こんな所も走りました
（真帆）はあ…
-Golden Gate Bridge.
-That's San Francisco!
（コユキ）
ゴールデンゲートブリッジです
（真帆）サンフランシスコだねー
あ これは？
-And this is...
-Seattle.
（コユキ）シアトルだよ
And that's Pike Place Market.
パイクプレイスマーケットです
（真帆）スーパー？
（コユキ）魚が飛ぶの
-A supermarket?
-You can see fish jumping.
And the Space Needle.
円盤です
And Jimi Hendrix.
ジミヘンです
千葉君が例の夢を見てさ
Chiba-kun had a dream.
And he heard Jimi say,
"Let's meet at my grave."
“墓場で会おう”って
聞いたんだ
（真帆）お墓？
-Grave?
-And the day was September 18.
（コユキ）そして この日が
ちょうど９月18日
-The day mentioned in Ryusuke's message.
-And also, the day Jimi Hendrix died.
（真帆）
竜介のメールにあった日だ
（コユキ）そして—
ジミ・ヘンドリックスの
命日でもあるんだ
Koyuki, you're cut off.
（真帆）あ コユキ 切れてるよ
（コユキ）ジミヘンのお墓だよ
-This is Jimi Hendrix's grave.
-Hmm...
And...we found Ryusuke.
（コユキ）そして 僕たちは
竜介君を見つけたんだ
Beck and Keith, too?
（真帆）ベックとキースもだね
Yep.
（真帆）アハハ またピンボケ
It's blurred again.
あー これ 新聞の記事
Oh, this is the newspaper article.
（真帆）
レオンって捕まったんだ？
-So Leon was arrested.
-And Ryusuke was right there.
（コユキ）竜介君
その現場にいたんだって
I'm so glad he's alive!
（真帆）兄貴
生きててよかった～
-Oh, you saw this already.
-Yeah.
（コユキ）あ これはもう見たね
（コユキ）そして…
And...we met up with Ryusuke,
who had Lucille,
俺たちは
ルシールを持った竜介君と—
at the Crocodile Cafe in Seattle.
シアトルのクロコダイル・カフェで
再会した
It was the first time all five members
were together since coming to America.
アメリカに来て初めて
メンバー５人がそろったんだ
これが BECKだ
Now this is BECK!
-Koyuki, let's do "Slip Out."
-Right.
（竜介）コユキ
「slip out(スリップアウト)」いくぞ！
I don't know since when I changed
to such a cold-hearted guy.
I have to warm this frozen icy
lonely heart to thaw.
I like being wrapped with warmness
more than anything else for sure.
I'm gonna make my coming days
to be filled with laughter and joy
（コユキ）お おい 何してんだ？
Hey, what're you doing?!
やめろよ いじめるのは
I let myself down that I'm more cruel
then I thought I would be.
Stop teasing him!
（子ども）うっせーな！
みんな 行こうぜ！
I let myself down that I'm more cruel
then I thought I would be.
Shut up! Let's go, everyone!
Beck! Come here!
（竜介）ベック！ カムヒア！
I told you,
you shouldn't go out alone.
You...
You made me worry.
A foreigner?
（コユキ）外国… の… 人？
（竜介）ハッハ～
気持ち悪いだろ この犬
Isn't this dog ugly?
Thank you for saving Beck.
ありがとう ベック助けてくれて
Sorrow isn't what I am,
but its growing my sensation
Regrets taught me how
to make any hard decisions.
Peace is always by my side
but I've never felt it once.
Love is not the word only
for the sweet romance. Yeah.
Well I'm scared, I'm scared,
I'm scared, I'm scared to death.
And I'm scared to keep on
going on my way. Yeah.
Well I'm scared, I'm scared,
I'm scared, I'm scared to death.
And I tell myself
I'm special till the end.
I don't give my heart to no one
cause I don't wanna waste my time.
I tried to love this loneliness
to slip out of lonesome hole.